What is it about me? Do I not look fun enough?
我是哪里不对？ 我看起来不够有趣吗？
Is there something repellent about me?
我是有哪里讨人厌吗？
How was the party?
派对好玩吗？
It couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed through me.
难玩死了 有个女人对我大送秋波
What is it? Am I hideously unattractive?
我有那么不讨人喜欢吗？
No,you are not. You are very attractive.
不，才怪
I go through the same thing.
我也是一样
When I put on a little weight, I question everything.
每当我增加了一点点重量 我就开始质疑一切了
I've put on weight?
你说我变胖了？
Did you want to...?
你要…？
No,not weight. More like insulation.
不是，不是重量 说绝缘体比较恰当
I'm unemployed, in dire need of a project.
钱德，我正在失业 迫切需要做点事情
Wanna work out? I can remake you.
你要不要运动？我可以重塑你
I would,but that might get in the way of my lying-around time.
我很想，但那或许会妨碍 我那些无所事事的时间
Please?
拜托啦
Come on,let her do it!
对啦，让她做一下嘛
All right.
好吧…
If we put on spandex and my boobs are bigger than yours,I'm going home.
但我穿上紧身衣后 胸部比你大的话，我就不来了
Your boobs are fine.
你的胸部很好呀
I shouldn't have said anything.
听着，我们不该乱开乌鸦嘴的
Come here. Come here!
过来…
Can't make hands meet!
双手都合不起来了
The One Where Ross Finds Out
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第07集 罗斯发现瑞秋对他有意思
Let's do it!
好，开始吧
What?
怎么了？
Nothing. Just never seen your little stretchy pants before.
没什么 只是没看过你穿紧身裤而已呀
And we're changing.
我去换衣服
Come on,give me five more!
加油，再做五个
Five more!
再五个
Five more and I'll flash you.
做就给你看波波
One...
一…
...two...
…二…
...two and a half.
…二点五
Just show me one of them.
好了，给我看一边吧
中央公园
She's insane!
她疯了
The woman is insane.
那个女人疯了
It's before work,after work, and during work.
上班前，上班后，上班中
She's got me doing butt-clenches at my desk.
她叫我在公司做收臀运动
And now they won't bring me my mail anymore.
现在，他们不再送邮件给我了
Hey,Pheebs. How'd it go with Scott?
菲菲，你昨晚跟史考怎么样？
It was nice. Took him to a romantic restaurant...
不错呀 带他去一家浪漫的餐厅…
...ordered champagne. Nice.
…点了香槟，很好
He still won't put out?
那个砘锘故遣恍卸啊？
Nope. Zilch. Nothing.
不，零蛋，没有
Sorry,Pheebs.
真遗撼，菲菲
Look,I don't mind taking it slow.
我不在乎慢慢的来
I like him a lot.
我很喜欢他
He's really interesting, and he's really sweet.
他这个人很有趣，人也很甜
Why won't he give it up?
他干嘛那么矜持呢？
Maybe he drives his car on the other side of the road.
或许他跟我们反方向开车
If you know what I mean.
你懂我的意思吧？
No. What do you mean? He's not British.
不懂，他又不是英国人
Maybe he's gay.
他或许是同性恋
I don't think that's the problem.
不，我觉得问题不在那儿
We went dancing the other night...
因为我们前几天去跳舞…
...and just the way he held me so close and looked into my eyes....
…他紧紧抱住我的那个样子 还有他凝视我眼睛的样子…
I just definitely felt something.
我觉得他对我绝对有意思
But how much can you tell from a look?
是啊，从眼神能看出多少呢？
I felt it on my hip. I could tell.
不，我是从屁股感觉到的
Yo,Bing! Racquetball in 20 minutes.
钱兄弟，二十分钟后打壁球
Joey,be a pal. Lift up my hand and smack her with it.
乔伊，好兄弟 举起我的手赏她一巴掌
Oh,Rachel! Don't look.
瑞秋，你别看
What?
什么？
I don't care. I have a date tonight.
我才不在乎 我今晚有约会
You have a date?
你有约会？
Monica's setting me up.
对呀，摩妮卡介绍的
What about Ross and....
那罗斯跟…
What? My whole insane jealousy thing?
我打翻醋坛子那码子事啊？
Well,you know, as much fun as that was...
虽然那还挺有趣的…
... I've decided to opt for sanity.
…我决定不再疯下去了
You're okay about all this?
你真的不介意那些了？
Oh,yeah,come on! I'm moving on.
少来了，我还要过我的日子呢
He can press her up against that window as much as he wants.
他爱怎么把她压在那扇窗子上 就怎么压吧
For all I care,he can throw her through the damn thing.
干脆把她摔过窗子算了
Hi,guys.
各位
Monica,I'll come by tomorrow and pick up Fluffy's old cat toys,okay?
摩妮卡，我想明天早上过来 拿膨胀以前的猫玩具
If you say his full name.
不讲全名就不给喔
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toys?
好吧，那我明天可不可以 过来拿喵喵膨膨的猫玩具？
All right.
没问题
-You're getting a cat? -Actually,we're getting a cat.
你要养猫啊？ 事实上，是我们要养猫
Together?
一起养？
Both of you? Together?
你们两个？一起？
It'll live with Ross half the time and with me half the time.
我们想它会一半时间跟罗斯住 一半跟我住
Well,isn't that just lovely?
那是不是很棒呢
That's something you'll enjoy...
那是一件你们两个…
...for a really,really, really long time.
…可以疼爱非常非常久的东西
Hopefully.
希望如此
Look at that. I gotta go! I got a date!
我得走了 我有约会
With a man.
跟个男人喔
You guys have a really good night...
祝各位今晚顺利…
...and you two have a really good cat.
…而你们两个得到一只好猫
We're not supposed to take these when we leave.
顺手牵羊是不对的
I don't know if Monica told you,but this my first date since my divorce.
我不晓得摩妮卡有没有告诉你 这是我离婚之后的第一次约会
If I seem a little nervous...
我显得有一点紧张…
... I am.
…那是真的
How long do cats live?
猫能活多久啊？
I'm sorry?
你说什么？
Cats. How long do they live?
猫，猫能活多久？
Figuring you don't throw them under a bus or something?
如果不把它们丢到 巴士下面去送死的话
Maybe 1 5,1 6 years.
大概是十五，六年吧
Well,that's just great.
那真是太棒了
Cheers!
干杯
Right. Clink.
好，干杯
Monica told you I was cuter than this,didn't she?
摩妮卡把我吹得比本人可爱 对不对？
No,Michael,it's not you. Sorry. It's just....
不，麦克 不是因为你…
It's this thing.
我是…我另外有心事
It's not as bad as it sounds...
事情说不定没那么糟啦…
... but this friend of mine is getting a cat with his girlfriend.
…我有一个朋友 他跟他的女朋友要养猫
Oh,that does sound....
听起来的确是…
He just started going out with her.
他们两个才刚刚开始交往不久
Is this guy an old boyfriend?
他是你以前的男朋友吗？
Yeah,he wishes.
他想得美喔
I'm sorry. Look at me.
对不起，你瞧瞧我
Michael,let's talk about you.
好了，麦克，谈谈你吧
So....
那么…
Did you ever get a pet with a girlfriend?
以前你跟女朋友 一起养过宠物吗？
-So I figured it out. -What?
我知道为什么了 什么？
Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me.
史考为什么不想跟我上床
I'm not sexy enough.
因为我不够性感
Phoebe,that's crazy.
菲比，别傻了
When I first met you, you know what I said?
第一次看到你之后 你知道我对钱德说什么吗？
I said,"Excellent butt,great rack."
我说“前突后翘，有看头”
Really? That's so sweet.
真的？嘴好甜
I mean,I'm officially offended. But that's so sweet.
说实在的，我被冒犯了 可是感觉真好
If you wanna know what the deal is, you're gonna have to ask him.
菲菲，你想知道为什么的话 你必须开口去问他
You're right. You're right.
你说得对…
You are so "yum"!
你真棒耶
I mean,it's a cat,you know? It's a cat.
那是只猫 你知道的，猫
Why can't they get a bug? One of those fruit flies.
他们干嘛不养只昆虫 养只果蝇就好了
Those things that live for a day.
那种只活一，两天的东西
What are they called?
它们叫什么？
Fruit flies?
果蝇？
Thank you.
谢谢
Would you like dessert?
要不要点甜点啊？
No dessert.
不，不要了
Just the check. Please.
我想结账
Oh,no. You're not having fun,are you?
你玩得不开心？
No,no,I am.
不…我很开心
But only because I've been playing the movie Diner in my head.
不过刚才那一个半小时 我都在回忆“餐馆”的情节
Oh,look at me.
你看我
Look at me.
I'm on a date with a really great guy.
我在跟一个很棒的男人约会
All I can think about is Ross...
却满脑子是罗斯…
...and his cat...
…跟他的猫…
...and his Julie.
…还有他的茱莉
I just want to get over him. Why can't I do that?
我只是想忘了他 天啊，为什么我不能呢？
Look,I've been through a divorce. Trust me,you're gonna be fine.
听我说，我经历过离婚 相信我，不会有事的
You can't see it because you haven't had closure
你还看不出来 因为你跟他还没有了结嘛…
Closure!
了结！
That's what it is! That's what I need!
就是那个，我就需要那个
God,you're brilliant!
天啊，你太棒了
Why didn't I think of that? How do I get that?
我为什么没有想到？ 我要怎么了结？
Well,there's no one way really,it's just....
这没有一定的方法，这只是…
Whatever it takes so that you can finally say to him:
你要用任何的方法 只要能让你对他说：
"I'm over you."
“我不在乎你了”就行了
Over you.
不在乎你
That's what it is.
就是这个
Closure.
了结
Hello? Excuse me?
抱歉
Excuse me. Hel
抱歉…
-Hang on. -Excuse me?
请稍等 对不起啊
-What? -Hi. I'm sorry.
什么？ 对不起
I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.
我需要跟你借一下电话
-I'm talking. -I see that.
我正在讲耶 我看得出来
One phone call,I'll be very quick. I'll even pay for it myself.
我打一个电话就可以了 很快的，我甚至会付钱给你
You're being a little weird about your phone.
你对你的电话有点诡异耶
All right. Fine.
好…
I'll call you back.
我待会儿再打给你
Thank you.
谢了
Machine.
答录机
-Just waiting for the beep. -Good.
我在等哔哔 太好了
Ross! Hi,it's Rachel.
罗斯，我是瑞秋
I'm just calling to say that...
我只是打来说…
...everything's fine.
…一切都很好
And I'm really happy for you...
我为你…
...and your cat.
…还有你的猫感到高兴
Who,by the way,I think you should name Michael.
对了，我认为你应该叫他麦克
You see there, I'm thinking of names...
知道吗？你瞧 我在想名字…
...so obviously I am over you.
…所以显然我不在乎你了
I am over you.
我不在乎你了
And that,my friend, is what they call "closure."
这就是我那位朋友 所谓的“了结”
It's Sunday morning. I'm not running on a Sunday.
摩妮卡，今天是礼拜天早上 礼拜天我绝不跑步
-Why not? -Because it's Sunday!
为什么？ 因为是礼拜天
It's God's day.
是神的日子
If you say stop,then we stop.
你说停我们就停
Stop.
停
No,come on! We can't stop!
不，别这样啦，我们不能停
We got three more pounds to go!
还有三磅要减
I am the energy train and you are on board!
我是精力火车而你在车上
And how was the date?
你的约会怎么样啊？
I think there was a restaurant.
我记得有家餐厅
I know there was wine.
我还记得有酒
Actually,Julie's getting a cab.
事实上，茱莉在楼下叫计程车
I just need the cat toys. Did Monica say....
我想要拿猫玩具 摩妮卡有没有说…
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
你为什么那样看我？
I'm sorry. I don't know,l....
对不起，我不知道…
I feel like I dreamed about you last night...
我觉得我昨晚好像梦到你…
... but I don't remember.
…但我不记得了
There they are.
在这儿
Did we speak on the phone? Did you call me?
我们昨晚有通电话吗？ 你有没有打给我？
No. I stayed at Julie's last night.
没有，我昨晚住在茱莉那里
I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?
事实上，我根本还没回家呢 你介意我听一下留言吗？
Oh,yeah,go ahead.
请便啊
Rach,I got a message from you!
阿秋，我有你的留言
Who's Michael?
麦克是谁啊？
Oh,my God!
天啊
Ross,no! Hang up the phone. Give me the phone!
天啊，罗斯，把电话挂掉
Give me the
电话给我…
You're over me?
你不在乎我了
Oh,God!
天啊
-You're -Oh,God.
你… 我的天啊…
You're over me?
你不在乎我了？
When were you...
你是什么时候…
... under me?
…在乎我的？
Rachel,do you...?
阿秋，你…？
I mean,were you?
我是说，你…你…？
What?
什么？
Basically...
基本上…
...Iately,I've....
…最近我…
I've sort of had feelings for you.
我对你有一些感觉
You've had feelings for me?
你对我有感觉？
So? You had feelings for me first!
那又怎样？你先对我有感觉的
You know about my You know I had
你知道我…
You know?
我是说，你知道我有…
Chandler told me.
钱德告诉我的
When did he? When did he? When did he?
钱德，他什么时候，他…
When you were in China.
你在中国的时候
Meeting Julie.
认识茱莉时
Julie. That's Oh,God!
茱莉？茱莉？那… 天啊
I need to lie down.
我需要躺下来
No,I'm gonna stand.
不，你知道，我要站着
I'm gonna stand...
我要站着…
...and I'm gonna walk. I'm walking and I am standing.
…我要踱步 我踱步，而且我站着
Now you're over me?
现在你不在乎我了？
Are you over me?
你还在乎我吗？
That's Julie.
那…那是茱莉
-Hi,Julie. -I've got a cab waiting.
茱莉 甜心，计程车在等喔
I'll be right down!
我马上下来
Wait,so you're going?
等等，你要走了？
Well,okay,I have to. I can't deal with this right now.
对，我得走 我现在没有办法谈这个
I mean,I've You know,I've got a cab.
计程车在等着
I've got a girlfriend. I'm gonna go get a cat.
我有女朋友 我要去领养一只猫
Cat!
猫
-Hey,Joey. -Hey,Pheebs.
乔伊 菲比
How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?
你为什么在看 犹太牧师弹电吉他？
I can't find the remote.
我找不到遥控器
Thank you.
谢谢
Scott asked me to come over for lunch and I did.
对了，史考约我去他家午餐 我去了
-And? -And we did.
然后… 我们做了
All right! Way to go!
正点，菲比好耶
Yea,me!
对呀
So how did it happen?
怎么发生的？
I took your advice and asked him what was going on.
我听了你的建议 问他到底怎么回事啊？
What did he say?
那他说什么？
He understands how sex can be a very emotional thing for a woman.
他了解性对女人而言呢 可以说是一件非常情绪化的事
And he was just afraid that I was going to get all:
他只是怕我会变得像…
"ls he gonna call me the next day?" and "Where is this going?"
“第二天是否会打电话给我” “我们会有结局吗”之类的
So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be serious.
所以他说他想等到 他准备开始认真了以后再说
So I said,"Okay. Relax,please."
所以我说“放轻松好吗？”
Sex can be just about two people right there in the moment.
我是说，性可以只是 两个人一时的感觉
If he wants to see me again,he can call. If not,that's fine too.
若他想再见我可以打电话给我 如果不想的话也没关系
So after a lot of talking...
所以在长谈之后…
... I convinced him.
…我说服他了
Let me get this straight.
让我先搞清楚
He got you to beg to sleep with him.
他让你求他跟你上床
He got you to say he never has to call you again.
他让你说 他永远不用再打电话给你
And he got you thinking this is a great idea?
而且还让你觉得 这是一个好主意？
This man is my god!
我简直崇拜他
I didn't get a cat.
我没有领养猫
That's interesting.
真有趣
No,it's not "interesting." It's very,very not interesting.
不，那一点都没有趣 那非常非常没有趣
It's actually 100% the opposite of interesting.
事实上那百分之百是 有趣的相反，瑞秋
I got it,Ross.
好，我懂了，罗斯
You had no right to say you had feelings for me.
你没有权利告诉我说 你曾经喜欢过我
I was doing great with Julie before I knew!
在我发现之前 我跟茱莉过得很快乐
I was doing great before I knew about you!
在我发现之前 我也过得很快乐
You think it's easy to see you with Julie?
你以为看你跟茱莉那样 我心里好受吗？
You should've said something before!
你应该在我认识她之前说出来
I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything?
那时我不知道啊 那你为何从不说什么呢？
There was never a good time.
因为总没有机会
You only had a year. And we only hung out every night!
对，你有一年机会 我们每晚都在一起混
Not...
不是…
...every night.
…每个晚上
It's not like I didn't try. But things got in the way.
而且我也不是没试过，瑞秋 但是每次都有事情发生
You know,like ltalian guys...
就像是意大利人啊…
...or ex-fiances...
…或者是前任的未婚夫啦…
...or ltalian guys.
…或者意大利人啊
There was one ltalian guy,okay? And do you have a point?
只有一个意大利人 你到底有没有重点啊？
The point is,I don't need this right now!
重点是 我现在已经不需要这个了
Okay? It's too late.
太迟了
I'm with somebody else. I'm happy. This ship has sailed!
我在跟别人交往，我很快乐 这艘船开航了
You're just gonna put away your feelings for me?
你喜欢什么时候搁开感情 都可以吗？
I've done it since ninth grade. I'm good at it.
我从初三就开始这样了 我早驾轻就熟了
All right,fine. You go ahead and do that.
那好，你尽管去做吧，罗斯
I don't need your ship!
我告诉你，我不需要你的蠢船
-Good. -Good!
好 好
And you know what? Now I got closure!
你知道吗？我现在了结了
Try the bottom one.
试试下面那个
Monica,it's 6:30 in the morning.
摩妮卡，现在是早上六点半
We're not working out. It's over.
我们不再去运动，结束了
No way! With one pound to go? Come on!
怎么啦？只剩一磅，来啦
We're workin',we're movin' We're in the zone,we're groovin'
我们运动，我们移动 我们在其中舞动
I don't mind the last pound.
我不在乎我的最后一磅
In fact,I kind of like the last pound.
我很喜欢这最后一磅
So don't make me do anything that I'll regret.
所以不要逼我 做下终生遗撼的事
What you gonna do,fat boy?
那你要做什么，肥仔？
What?
什么？
Nothing. Except tell you it's wonderful how much energy you have.
没什么，除了告诉你 我觉得你精力这么充沛真棒
Well,thanks.
谢了
Especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.
尤其是你现在去找工作 找得焦头烂额
You can't tell your parents you were fired,because they'd be disappointed.
你不能告诉你父母你被开除了 因为他们会非常的失望
It's not as if you have a boyfriend's shoulder to cry on.
尤其你又没有男朋友 可以借肩膀让你哭
Well,no. But l....
没有，但是我…
If it were me,I'd have difficulty getting out of bed at all.
我是说，如果是我的话 我想我会连起床都会很困难
You know,I try to stay positive.
我试着保持积极
So you....
那么…
You feel like going for a run?
你想出去跑一跑吗？
All right.
好吧
Because you don't have to. You could just take a nap right here.
你知道你不一定要去跑的 你可以在这里睡一下